http://www.hallmark.com/privacy/#section-do-not-sell

0
item(s) in your cart.
Wedding
Hanukkah (12/11)
Christmas (12/25)
Kwanzaa (12/26)
New Year’s Day (1/1)
Three King’s Day (1/6)
By Occasion or Holiday
Hanukkah (12/11)
Christmas (12/25)
Kwanzaa (12/26)
New Year’s Day (1/1)
Three King’s Day (1/6)
Wedding
Christmas (12/25)
Accessories
Add Photo(s)
By Occasions & Holidays
Hanukkah (12/11)
Christmas (12/25)
Celebrate Upcoming Holidays
Hanukkah (12/10 -12/18)
Christmas (12/25)
Kwanzaa (12/26)
New Year's Day (1/1)
Valentine's Day (2/14)
St. Patrick's Day (3/17)
Easter (4/4)
Mother's Day (5/9)
Father's Day (6/20)
Fourth of July (7/4)
Friendship Day (8/1)
Halloween (10/31)
Thanksgiving (11/26)
Hallmark's Privacy Statement
At Hallmark, we strive to help people create a caring and more connected world. Through our cards, products and services, we help people connect and enrich lives.
To do this, we use the information you’ve provided to us through your interactions with Hallmark, as well as the purchases you’ve made with us. This helps us create a more tailored experience just for you, helps us deliver coupons and offers, and helps us show you marketing that showcases the products and services we think you’d enjoy.
Hallmark currently does not, nor have we in the past, receive any money from third party companies in exchange for your personal information. Any information we share with others is to help provide you a quick and easy shopping experience and is not allowed to be shared with anyone else.
We treasure the special relationship we have with you and strive to maintain the trust you give us. If you’re still curious about what type of information Hallmark uses to create your specialized shopping experience, please continue by reading the full policy below.
Our privacy policy is reviewed regularly to make sure we continue to serve your privacy interests. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will inform you by posting a notice on our website. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our digital properties and will replace any prior policies.
Account Information
Information We Collect
How We Use Your Information
Security
California Consumer Privacy Act
Information We Collect
Right to Know
Right to Delete
Do Not Sell
Other California Privacy Rights
Nevada Consumer Opt-Out Requests
Personalized Messages
How to contact us
Account Information
How do I access and change my email contact preferences?
If you do not want to be contacted by Hallmark for promotional purposes, you may change your preferences at any time. First, make sure you are signed in to your Hallmark.com account. Then navigate to Communication Preferences within your account section. Uncheck the box next to the statement “Hallmark and its companies can email me about special offers and promotions.
How do I access and change my personal information?
You can change or delete your personal information anytime. Sign in to your Hallmark.com account. You can update any of your personal information by choosing what information you would like to update. Navigate to the Profile section to update your name, email, primary mailing address or password. You can also update shipping addresses and saved payment methods.
Address book and reminder notifications
Once you’ve created a user account at Hallmark.com, you have the chance to create an online address book to keep track of important addresses. Hallmark.com also lets you set reminders for important holidays and events. Your requested reminders may include links to our site for products or content you may find relevant. Address book and reminder notification information is highly confidential, and that information will not be used for third-party promotions.
Information We Collect
See how your information and your privacy help make up your Hallmark experience. At Hallmark, your information is used to create an easy and enjoyable shopping experience for you.
The information you provide to us is used to help create a more tailored experience to help you find products and experiences that we think you’d be interested in. This information is given to us when you create an account with any of our programs or services and when you shop with us. There are several ways we may collect information from you.
Information you provide directly to us:
Name
Email address
Shipping addresses
Mailing address
Phone number
Date of birth
Account information, including Crown Rewards number and KOC membership information
Messages and photographs provided by you for personalized cards and gifts
Information provided by you as you interact with the Customer Care team
Information provided by you as you provide feedback on products or services offered on our sites and apps
Information relating to transactions and products purchased, including payment information, billing address and purchase, return and exchange information
Information collected passively:
Device information, including device model, operating system version, device date and time, unique device identifiers, mobile network information
Geolocation of your device
How you use our sites and mobile applications, including search terms and pages you visit
Information from third parties:
Information we receive from business partners, including online advertising networks
Social media platforms, including Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Pinterest and Instagram.
How We Use Your Information
At Hallmark, we are committed to the security and privacy of your information. When you provide us with information about yourself, we only share that information with our partners, like the businesses which help process your orders, service providers (like delivery companies), and contractors. We give them this information to help fulfill your orders, offer you products and services, and other consumer service-based needs. Likewise, these companies provide information to us so we can provide you with product or service suggestions we think you might be interested in.
Hallmark allows certain companies to place tracking technologies like cookies and pixels on our sites, which allow these companies to receive information about your activity on our websites. Those companies may use that data to show you more relevant advertisements and promotions. Learn more about your ability to control privacy settings at the companies we work with, which include but are not limited to, Adobe, Facebook/Instagram, Verizon, LiveRamp, Pinterest and Google/YouTube.
You always have control over whether these technologies work on your devices. You can disable them entirely by opting-out of third-party cookies or using your mobile device ID for targeted advertising. You can also use preferences or settings on your device(s) to manage your privacy controls.
Any non-Hallmark company we work with is contractually not allowed to use this information in any other way. We value the trust you place in us, and this is one way we strive to preserve it.
Security
To protect your information, we use the same technology your bank uses to protect your information. For added security, we also use a digital secure server ID to protect you when you use our sites. In other words, the parties to whom we provide your information are people that help us help you. And we require them to join us in keeping your information safe.
While we are careful with how your information is treated and are selective when choosing other companies and websites with which we interact, any site Hallmark links to is out of our control. So when interacting with sites outside of Hallmark, please make sure to read their Privacy Policy before sharing your information with them.
California Consumer Privacy Act
Effective January 1, 2020, if you are a California resident, you have expanded rights regarding the collection and disclosure of information about yourself as part of the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (CCPA).
Only you or your authorized representative may make these requests. You may make requests for data disclosure or portability no more than twice in a 12-month period. In your request, you must provide enough information to allow us to verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information, or their authorized representative. You must also describe your request with enough detail so that we can understand, evaluate and respond to it. We can’t respond to your request if we can’t verify your identity. Making such a request does not require you to create an account with us, and we will only use the information you provide in a request to verify your identity. Authorized representatives must provide a signed, written permission to make such requests or power of attorney. You may also make a request on behalf of your minor child.
If you have questions about any of these rights, please call us at 1-877-203-2262.
We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights.
Information We Collect
Below are the categories and examples of information we collect, along with how we use that information. Unless otherwise noted, we collect this information from our users, customers and service providers. Unless otherwise noted, we use this information to enable use of our sites, services and products; to communicate with you; to understand how users interact with our site; and to improve our products and services. Unless otherwise noted, we may share this information with our service providers.
Identifiers such as name, mailing address, IP address, email address or account name. We may generate these identifiers internally, such as a Crown Rewards membership number.
Personal information categories such as name, signature, address or phone number. (Information in this category may overlap with other categories.)
Protected classification characteristics including age, gender, race, ethnicity, religion, marital status, and veteran/military status.
Internet/network activity, such as browsing history, search history, banners you click, and pages you visit on our site.
Commercial information such as what you purchase or consider purchasing from us and other requests you make. This information allows us to complete those transactions and deliver your orders in a timely manner.
Geolocation data, such as the location of your computer or mobile device. This helps us show you the nearest stores to your location.
Sensory data such as audio, electronic, visual or similar information.
Inferences drawn from other personal information may be generated internally. These inferences may include preferences, characteristics, predispositions and behaviors, and are used to help us provide you more relevant products and services and provide a better experience on our website and apps. We do not share this information.
We will not collect additional categories of personal information or use it in materially different purposes without providing you notice. Your personal information may be shared with third parties for business purpose (“service providers”). Service providers are required to keep the personal information confidential and not use it for any purpose other than what is specified in what is outlined in our contract with them.
Right to Know
In accordance with the CCPA, you have the right to know what information we have collected about you. You can request us to disclose this personal information no more than twice in a 12-month period. This information will be provided in an accessible format that allows you to transmit your data from one entity to another. If you would like a list of the information we maintain, we will email it to you within 45 days of your request. If we require more time (up to 90 days) we’ll let you know this, and the reason why, in writing. Visit Customer Care or call 1-877-203-2262 to proceed with this request.
Right to Delete
In accordance with the CCPA, you have the right to request that we delete the information we have about you. Hallmark offers several services that require certain information in order to work. Deleting your information can affect your ability to: • Earn exclusive offers and coupons • Maintain membership to Crown Rewards and Keepsake Ornament Club • Access services like Hallmark Movies Now and Hallmark eCards • Get the inside scoop on the exciting new surprises Hallmark is working on We will attempt to complete your request within 45 days. If we require more time (up to 90 days) we’ll let you know this, and the reason why, in writing. To proceed, visit Customer Care or call 1-877-203-2262 to provide the information we need to validate your request.
Do Not Sell
In accordance with the CCPA, if you are 16 years or older, you have the right to opt-out of the sale of your personal information. Consumers who we know are under 16 are already opted-out of this sale of information, unless they have specifically exercised their right to opt-in. A parent or guardian must provide an opt-in for consumers less than 13.
Hallmark does not now, nor have we in the past, sell consumer information to third parties for financial gain. What we sometimes do is to track your device by sending non-identifying information to partners, who then use it to provide you relevant marketing messages. When we do this, your personal information (name, phone number, etc.) is not shared with them.
Under the CCPA, sharing data for online advertising like this may be considered a “sale” of information, and we are required to allow you to opt out of selling your information. To help you manage the tracking of your information, including browsing history and targeted marketing efforts, you can take action by opting out of cookies and device ID tracking. Please read the “How We Use Your Information” section of the policy for more information on how you can manage your privacy via third parties. The Digital Advertising Alliance offers tools for California consumers to send requests under the CCPA to opt out of the sale of personal information by some or all of the participating companies. You can also manage privacy options directly in your device preferences or settings.
Other California Privacy Rights
California’s “Shine the Light” law (Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as S.B. 27) allows customers to opt out of having your personal information shared for direct marketing purposes. To make this request, you may write us at Hallmark Cards Consumer Care; P.O. Box 419034; Kansas City, MO 64141; or call 1-800-HALLMARK. Within 30 days of receiving your request, we will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding year, along with the names and addresses of those third parties. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted to locations other than those specified above.
Nevada Consumer Opt-Out Requests
Nevada S.B. 220 provides consumers with the ability to opt out of the sale of their personal information. We do not sell your personal information as defined in S.B. 220. However, should our practices change in the future and you wish to opt out, your request must be submitted to OptOut@hallmark.com. We will record your request and avoid selling your information at any point in the future.
Personalized Messages
Your ecards and personalized greeting card messages are kept confidential and secure. Ecards will only be accessed when it is necessary to complete your order. For order fulfillment, a representative may view your message. Once again, third parties are not allowed to use this information. They can only fulfill orders and help with your questions. We do reserve the right to work with law enforcement officials in the investigation of possible unlawful activities of our customers related to communications made on our site. We will have no legal responsibility for such disclosures.
How to Contact Us
You may contact us by using the Email Us or Chat links on our Customer Care site, or call us at 1-800-HALLMARK. The information you provide is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. We may also file your comments and share them with our customer care team to improve our service in the future. If you still have questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please write us at:
Hallmark Cards Consumer Care
P.O. Box 419034
Kansas City, MO 64141
